( WIND HOWLING )
Goddamn bunch of cutthroats .
Oh , shit .
Boy , they 'd leave me belly-up out here if they knew I was getting ready to run .
- Don 't you make a noise when you walk ? - Uh-uh .
Hey , wait a minute .
You got yourself all done up , Ruby .
- What are you up to ? - Here .
Oh , no you don 't . Uh-uh .
Ain 't no trading today , Ruby .
And not no more , neither .
You folks gone too far .
Trooper been snooping around .
Air Force been through here twice .
You folks have to go rob a goddamn Air Force PX for God 's sakes .
We 're hungry .
No one comes through back there anymore .
What did you get ?
Whiskey and radios . I ain 't got nothing to eat .
I 'm sorry , Ruby . I know you 're starving , but I ain 't got nothing else to trade .
I got no more gas , no more cartridges , no more food .
And the folks in Corn Creek have cut me off already .
They even talked of blocking off this whole section
and marching the National Guard through , see what they can find .
You coyotes better watch your p 's and q 's for a spell .
- Take me with you . - What ? ( LAUGHS )
So that 's it . You want to get out .
Do you think you could pass out there with the regular folks ?
You don 't know a knife and fork from your five fingers .
And you stink like a horse .
You 're getting out . You take me , too .
Does the pack know you 're doing this ?
Does Jupiter know ?
Why , he 'd cut you to pieces if I told him you were going over the hill .
If my pa knew you was getting out , he 'd rip your lungs out .
- MAN : Hello ? Anybody around ? - Get in here .
That 'll be the State Troopers .
They 'll toss you in jail and throw the key up a wild sow 's ass and holler , " Suey ! "
MAN : Well , I 'll take a look around . I don 't see any ...
Didn 't hear you . I was just cleaning up .
Fill it up and check the oil and water .
Give you what I got . Ain 't got much . I 'm just closing down .
Morning .
( DOGS BARKING )
Don 't you mind them , they just want to play .
Beauty , get down in there . Down now !
That 's ... That 's a good girl .
- ( BABY CRYING ) - Odd .
I 'm telling you , we 're in the middle of nowhere .
Yeah , I wonder how far it is to the nearest cheeseburger .
We don 't usually get folk up this way . Where you heading ?
California . L.A.
Movie stars and fancy cars .
California ?
You sure as hell off the beaten track for that .
Yeah , well , we 're just making a stop around here first .
You know this place around here ? The desert ?
Why ?
- MAN : You got a bathroom around here ? - Yeah , round in back . Round in back .
I need to make a litter dump . You got a place to throw some trash ?
Oh hell . Use the whole damn desert for all I care .
Oh , I 'm sorry , Bob . Do you have your key ?
Good .
How are my two baby girls doing ?
Fabulous .
( PIG SNORTS )
Hey , piggy , piggy .
( RATTLING )
WOMAN : So , anyway , we thought we 'd take a little detour and go see it .
It 's supposed to be a real silver mine .
Well , anyway , that 's why I was asking .
You see , it 's my Aunt Mildred 's gift to Bob and me on our silver anniversary ,
and that 's tomorrow .
Lady , they ain 't no silver left back in there .
Besides , the Air Force uses part of this as a gunnery range .
You folks just forget that foolishness and go onto California .
- That 'll be $ 6.80 . - OK .
- I 've got no change . - Oh , that figures .
- Detective , huh ? - That 's right .
Bob just retired from the police force .
He had to a little early because of his heart .
Referring to Strike Creek Road . Do you know where it is ?
Look , Mister , don 't take your family back in there .
The silver 's been gone 40 years now .
Besides , there 's nothing back in there but animals .
WOMAN : Animals ? You mean nobody lives back there ?
FRED : Nobody you 'd want to meet , lady , believe me .
( DOG WHINING )
See ? There 's nothing back here .
Jeeze ! Look at this place .
- ( DOG WHINING ) - What 's the matter ?
See something ?
Ugh !
- What ? - RUBY : Mercury !
I didn 't do anything wrong . I just came to trade .
Grandpa Freddy , he says he 's running away .
- ( DOG BARKS ) - Shh ! Big mouth .
MERCURY : Let 's go .
- ( DOG WHINES ) - Come here . Come here .
- ( DOG BARKS ) - Hold it . Come here . Shh !
( DOG BARKS )
Come on , Doug .
Come on . He must have some animals back there .
Shh .
There 's nothing , dummy .
- ( DOG WHINES ) - Come on . Come on .
Come on .
( CAR ENGINE STARTS )
( PLANE OVERHEAD )
DOUG : Yeah , you 'd better check your grandchildren there , Mister .
I think one of them 's cut himself on the window back there .
- FRED : I 'll check it . Thanks . - DOUG : That 's OK .
You folks go right to California and have a good trip .
You folks stay on the main road now , you hear ?
Stay on the main road !
( PLANE OVERHEAD )
MERCURY : Let 's get out of here .
What the fuck ?
Oh , Lord .
There 'll be hell to pay now .
MAN : Jupiter . Papa .
WOMAN : ( OVER RADIO ) Papa Hunter , identify .
MAN : Mama . Pluto .
You see a station wagon and a trailer ?
MAMA : ( OVER RADIO ) That 's what Mercury said ,
if you can believe him .
They coming .
We 're lost . The old creep told you not to get off the road .
The old bastard probably snuck up here and ripped off our mine
and that 's why he doesn 't want us up here .
We 'll be French fries , human French fries .
We are not going to be French fries .
We 're right here someplace on this little blue road .
Mother , this road is not a blue line .
It 's a dotted line if it 's on the map at all .
Oh , Jesus .
Nellis Air Force Base Nuclear Testing Site , closed to the public .
Holy shit , Daddy !
All right , everybody shuts up . That 's it .
Man alive .
We 're not on a bomb range and we 're not goddamn lost .
- And we are ... - ( PLANE ROARS PAST )
Jesus Christ on a crutch , what was that ?
- ( BABY CRIES ) - Daddy , slow down a little bit , will you ?
Daddy , we 're going to lose the trailer .
- Daddy , Mum is ... ! - ( EXPLOSION )
Bob , watch !
( BABY CRYING )
GIRL : You guys and your stupid silver mine .
Doug , are you OK ?
DOUG : Open the door . I think the door is jammed .
Why don 't you try unlocking it , creep ?
DOUG : Oh , I got it .
- Are you OK ? - I 'm all right .
( DOGS GROWLING )
I feel like I 've just been through my first California earthquake .
- How 's the baby ? - She 's fine . Mum 's got her .
I think we were lucky .
- My finches OK ? - Aren 't you even going to ask how I am ?
Oh , get out of my life , Bobby .
- Look , I 'm wounded . - What is it ? ( SCREAMS )
It 's just ketchup , folks .
Look out .
Oh , you 're so stupid .
DAD : Twenty-five years I 'm a cop
in the worst goddamn precinct in Cleveland .
Niggers shoot arrows at me
and the hillbillies throw dogs off the roofs at me .
I 'm even shot at on two separate occasions by my own men ,
but none of these bastards ever come as close to killing me
as my own goddamn wife and her goddamn road maps and her wrong turns
and her goddamn hysterical screaming and her ...
Watch your language .
You watch your heart , too . You know what Dr Springer said .
Dr Springer can take his stethoscope and shove it ...
into his little black bag sideways .
( BUZZARD SQUAWKS )
It 's a turkey buzzard .
It 's the janitor of the desert .
Does that mean there 's a town nearby ?
Like when sailors spot a bird at sea and know they 're near land ?
Yeah .
No .
( PANTING )
PLUTO : So pretty .
Pretty girl .
BOB : Threw the hitch right off the back .
What 's the verdict , big fella ?
- Well , the goddamn axle snapped . - Oh no .
Forget it . Forget it .
What do we do now ?
We walk , baby .
You know , Marlon Perkins says that rattlesnakes can reach lengths of 20 feet
and can kill you in eight minutes .
( CHUCKLES ) Then you better not shoot until you see the whites of their fangs , son .
- Or was it eight feet and 20 minutes ? - Oh , Ma .
Thank goodness the boys at the precinct
presented me with this howitzer when I retired .
Sure wouldn 't want to go looking for those pythons without it .
If it 's all the same to you , Bob Carter , I 'll put my faith in the good Lord
and a little gunpowder rather than coyotes and rattlesnakes .
This place must be crawling with them .
Well , Katy 's taking this all calmly .
You OK ?
I hate it out here .
It 's just uncomfortable . That 's all .
It 's more than uncomfortable .
DOUG : Lynne , honey , would you get me my jacket , please ?
( STOMPING )
( WHIMPERS IN DISGUST )
What is it ?
Nothing .
BOBBY : I don 't get it . Why can 't we raise anybody on the CB ?
Here .
It looks to me like these hills are full of iron ,
and if that 's the case , you 're not going to get a radio signal past them .
Would you hold this please ?
I 'm going to head North ,
something on the map that looks like a military installation here .
OK , fine .
MUM : You ought to have a gun too , Doug .
We only have two guns , and I think one of them ought to stay with you guys .
All right , Doug . You walk out six or seven miles and get back .
I 'll walk out as far as the old geezer 's service station , and ...
MUM : You can 't get there and back before dark .
It 's only 15 miles back .
Sweetheart , I 'll get there about sundown .
If the old guy 's there , I 'll borrow his pickup . If he 's not there , I 'll borrow his phone .
But what if the old jerk doesn 't have a phone ?
- Then I 'll pawn it . - Daddy , don 't .
Look , you stay close to the trailer , and don 't bust Bobby 's chops .
- He is in charge . - That creep isn 't in charge of me .
Hey ! Another outburst like that , and I 'll confine you to quarters .
All right , men , synchronise the watches . It 's 3 : 38 .
If you 're not back by midnight , we 'll have to board the submarine without you .
Can we have a word of prayer first ?
- Oh , mother , for crying in a bucket . - Brenda !
Just to ask the Lord to watch over us all .
Is that too much to ask ?
Bob ?
Heavenly Father , watch over us for the rest of this day .
Keep us in thy care in Jesus ' name .
Amen .
So long , troops .
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
MAMA : ( OVER RADIO ) Pluto ?
PLUTO : They stuck good , easy pickings now .
( WHINING )
BOBBY : Beauty ! Come here , girl .
Come on , Beauty . Come on , Beauty .
Beauty . Come on , Beauty .
Come on , girl . Let 's go .
Well , at least it 's cooler now .
- Oh , bring some plates would you , Bob ? - Sure .
( WHINING )
- MUM : It is cooler , isn 't it ? - Oh , yeah . Fantastic !
Now we 'll all freeze to death .
This is a great way to spend the eve of your 25th wedding anniversary .
BRENDA : Frozen French fries .
A huge clump of human French fries
was found stuck to a camper trailer this morning by ...
But who 'd ever find us ?
Well , it 's kind of a pretty place .
There 's certainly plenty of the sunshine and fresh air .
- This much fresh air 's unhealthy . - Oh , it 's good for you .
It makes me want to puke , if you really want to know .
( SIGHS ) It gives me the creeps .
I suppose it 's my fault we got lost .
Mother , don 't be ridiculous .
It was Daddy 's idea to go looking around for this mine without any help .
We 'd be in California by now if we 'd stayed on the interstate .
Showers and gin and tonics .
- BRENDA : The beach . - LYNNE : Fresh clothes .
( WHINING )
I wonder what 's bugging her ?
Maybe there 's some rattlesnakes prowling around .
You know what Freud would say about your obsession with rattlesnakes , Ma ?
I wonder why the beast isn 't chiming in .
Beast never barks until he 's ready for the kill .
He likes to catch his victims unawares .
Hey , you know you 're right . Remember that poodle he killed in Miami ?
- BOBBY : Do I ? - Oh boy , was that lady ever fit to be tied .
Was Daddy ever mad .
He had to pay vet bills for a dead poodle .
All right , creep , what 's your story ?
BOBBY : Brenda , don 't .
Beauty !
Beauty , get back here !
Bobby !
Beauty !
( BARKING )
MAN : Here , Beauty .
Here , Beauty . Come here . Come here , girl .
BOBBY : Beauty !
MAN : Hey , pig , come here .
Beauty , come here .
BOBBY : Beauty !
Beauty !
Hey , girl .
( BARKING )
Beauty !
( HOWLING )
MUM : Bobby !
Do you hear him answer ?
No .
Bobby , come down .
Beauty ?
( FRED 'S VOICE , DISTORTED ) You folks stay on the main road now , you hear ?
Stay on the main road .
Nothing out there but animals .
Animals .
Animals . Animals .
( GROWLING , SCREAMING )
Ooh ...
- Here . - Oh , thanks .
It must have dropped 20 degrees in the last hour .
God , I thought I was out .
MUM : Hello . Testing .
Hello ? Anybody there ?
Testing , testing .
Maypole , maypole , maypole , maypole .
This is Mama Bear Carter calling .
Do any of you bears have your ears up ?
Gosh , I can 't seem to remember how this works .
- It 's ' mayday ' , Mum , not ' maypole ' . - Hmm ?
- Mayday . - Oh .
- Did you put it on battery ? - Mm-hmm .
Well , here , let me .
Mayday , mayday .
This is mobile unit 2345 CB .
We are stranded and in need ofhelp .
Do you copy ?
( HEAVY BREATHING OVER RADIO )
What the hell was that ?
It sounded like some sort of animal .
Yeah , well , animals around here are smart enough to run radios ,
we 're up shit creek without a paddle .
You know you never used language like that
before you moved to New York City .
Where 's Bobby and the men , anyway ?
Brenda ?
Bobby !
Beast , come back here . ( YELPS )
Beast .
Bobby ?
LYNNE : Brenda ? You there ?
Just a minute , Lynne .
Bobby ?
( CLANKING )
How does this damn thing work anyway ?
Bobby ?
( SCREAMS )
Bobby , where have you been ?
Bobby , your face ... What happened ?
Bobby ?
( HOWLING )
( DIAL TONE )
( LINE DISCONNECTS )
( RATTLING )
( CHOKING )
Get your stupid neck out of that belt , you jackass .
( COUGHING )
Should have left you hanging after you took a shot at me .
Not until you tell me what the hell is going on .
You 're trespassing , that 's what . Give me that .
You always try to stop trespassers by hanging yourself ?
I thought you was somebody else .
- How 's your family ? - Well ...
The car skidded off the road , we broke an axle .
They 're back at the trailer . They 're all OK .
Like hell they are . Give me that booze .
There 's something you should know about .
Yeah , well , what is it ?
BOBBY : Come on , Beast .
Daddy and Doug back yet ?
Not yet .
Didn 't you find Beauty ?
She must have run off .
Give me that .
Come on , Beast .
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
- MUM : Come on , sweetheart ... - ( RUSTLING )
Back in ' 29 , this place was spanking new ,
and me and my wife Martha had a little baby girl
so pretty and good , we couldn 't believe ,
and another kid on the way .
But when Martha had this one , something went wrong .
This thing she give me , something happened .
( SOBBING ) He was so big ...
He came out sideways and almost tore poor Martha apart .
( SOBS )
He weighed 20 pounds and was hairy as a monkey .
When he was 10 years old ,
he was big as I was .
Accidents were happening all the time .
Dogs falling in the well .
I even found chickens with their heads bit off .
Then in August of ' 39 ,
I was in town getting supplies ,
and the whole damn house burned to the ground .
My little baby girl was a cinder when I found her ,
but this monster kid wasn 't even singed .
I knew he 'd done it .
I hit him with a tyre iron , and I split his face wide open .
How bad was it ?
I thought I 'd killed him .
I was afraid they 'd come and take me away ,
so I took him out in the desert and I left him there .
I figured if he wasn 't dead ,
he couldn 't live more than two hours out there in that heat .
Then it would all be over with .
And you think his ghost is still trying to track you ?
That was a long time ago .
Long enough for him to steal a whore that nobody would miss .
Long enough to raise a passel of wild kids .
Long enough for a devil kid to grow up to be a devil man .
( CLANKING )
What the hell is this ?
- That 's just some stuff that I ... - ( ROARING )
( DOOR SLAMS SHUT )
( SCREAMS )
You want some cheese on this ? There 's plenty left .
I don 't want anything .
What 's the matter , don 't you feel well ?
I 'm just not hungry .
- Your face still bothering you ? - No .
- Did anybody try to CB while I was gone ? - MUM : We tried .
We tried . Nothing ...
Well , one time we got something that sounded an Epstein caller .
What do you mean ?
Well , it sounded sort of like heavy breathing , didn 't it , Mum ?
It , er ... it was static .
It wasn 't .
( BANG )
What was that ?
( COCKS GUN )
Aw , Jesus .
What 's going on ?
( MAN SHOUTING IN DISTANCE ) Mummy !
Daddy !
Help me !
Bogeyman get me !
Daddy ! ( LAUGHS )
You son of a bitch !
( LAUGHING )
MAN : Faster . Faster .
Mummy , Daddy . Faster .
Your chest hurt ? Faster . Faster .
( LAUGHS )
Looks like Daddy going to fall down .
Over here .
Over here . ( LAUGHS )
Here .
( GROANS )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
Daddy all gone ?
( LAUGHING )
( WHISPERS ) Daddy all gone ?
Pluto .
- PLUTO : ( OVER RADIO ) Papa Jupe ? - Papa Jupe .
We about ready .
( COUGHS )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( COCKS GUN )
Hey .
You mind pointing that thing somewhere else ?
Oh .
Thank you .
( WHISTLES ) It gets cold out there .
Here , I brought you a present .
What 's the matter with you ?
Well , for one thing , Dad 's not back yet .
Oh , hell .
I wouldn 't expect him this early .
He had a lot further to go than I did .
Besides , it 's slow-going out there .
Where are the dogs ?
Beast broke his chain about an hour ago and he ran off .
Oh , yeah ?
And Beauty ...
Well ...
- Beauty , sh ... - It 's Doug .
Hey !
Doug 's back !
I knew when you smelled food you 'd show up !
Hey , gorgeous .
Get out of here .
- How you doing ? - Did you find anything ?
Oh , yeah . Lots of stuff . There 's , er ...
I found a tower and a dump about five miles out of here .
All kinds of good stuff . Look at this !
Look at all of this . I mean , it 's no wonder we 're paying higher taxes .
They 're throwing this stuff away .
Did you go any further ? Did you find any people ?
Oh , no . There 's no people .
And I couldn 't go any further because the road just stops right there .
Just ended right there .
- Is there any food left ? I am so hungry . - Oh , come and get it .
- Come on . - OK .
Listen , we got to go out there
'cause there 's enough stuff to open an army surplus store ,
honest to God .
Ma ?
( BARKING )
( DOG HOWLING )
What 's the matter ? You don 't like dog anymore ?
I like it .
Maybe dog 's too good for a runaway slut like you .
The dog 's ghost is talking out there tonight .
( LAUGHS )
( DOG HOWLING )
Another dog .
Great big stud .
Mama .
Mama ?
Let me come inside ?
Goodies around here
means he ain 't around there .
Where ?
Never you mind .
( GAGGING )
( GROANING )
MOTHER : Bobby ? Come on in .
Don 't catch a cold .
- Are you sure you 're all right ? - I 'm fine .
OK .
Don 't lock that too hard , old bean , we 're going out in a second .
- Hey , where you going ? - The sack .
I don 't think you should sleep in the station wagon tonight .
- Why not ? - Look , sleep in here on the floor .
- What are you , nuts ? - Look , Doug , I 've got to talk to you .
- All set ? - Yeah . All set .
Hey . I guarantee you that he 'll be back here by 9 : 30 .
Bobby 's worried that rattlesnakes are going to get Big Bob .
- It isn 't that . - Hey .
You better worry about what Big Bob will do to the rattlesnakes .
Come on , you .
Uh ...
Listen . If he 's not back here by 11 o 'clock , we 'll go out and meet him , OK ?
Sleep well .
( # GENTLE MUSIC PLAYS )
( WHISPERS ) I 'm scared .
( CHUCKLING )
( DOG BARKING )
Beast ?
( BARKING )
Beast ! Come here , boy ! Come on !
( GROWLING )
- ( WHINING ) - Beast ?
( YELPING )
Ugh !
Beast ?
Hey , boy .
( GROWLING )
Come here , boy .
Just ...
( WHINING )
( SHEEP BLEATING )
Come on .
( IMITATES COW )
Ugh ! Ha ...
( DOG WHINES )
( GENTLE MOANING )
( KISSING )
Stupid ...
( MOANING )
Jesus !
( GIGGLING )
LYNNE : What do you want ?
I mean , the amount of privacy we get on this trip has been zero .
I 'm not the one knocking on windows in the middle of the night .
All right , this better be good .
- I need your keys . - Oh , for crying out loud !
I locked myself out .
- Couldn 't you wait ? - Goddamnit ! Give me the keys , please !
Look , something weird is going on around here .
Dad 's not back yet .
You said that you heard heavy breathing on the CB ,
and now Beast is out there barking like he 's hurt .
Oh , Bobby , it 's probably Beauty .
She always sounds like that when she barks .
- ( SOBS ) Beauty is dead . - What ?
She 's been dead since this afternoon .
Beauty 's dead ?
What happened ? Why didn 't you tell us sooner ?
( SOBS ) I tried .
When I found her she 'd been gutted .
Somebody slit her .
It was pretty bad .
I ... I was so scared , I ran away .
OK .
You just hold on right here . I 'll get a flashlight , and we 'll take a look .
OK . Hang on . Come on , come on .
- You stay here . - I will not stay here .
( RATTLING )
Do it .
( BOB SHOUTING ) Oh , my God !
Oh , God . Ethel !
Help me , Ethel !
Oh , God ! Help me !
- Ethel , don 't go out there . - Let me go !
- Ma ! - BOB : Put it out !
Brenda ?
Brenda ? Keep an eye on the baby , OK ?
BOB : Oh , my God !
Ethel !
Help me , Ethel ! Help me !
Papa Jupiter . This here is Mars .
PAPA JUPE : You and Pluto in , Mars ?
We in , Papa . We in .
( SCREAMING )
Help me !
God !
( SCREAMING )
Oh , my God !
BOB : Ethel !
( SCREAMING )
( GROWLING )
( BRENDA SCREAMING )
( PLUTO LAUGHING )
( SCREAMING )
You son of a bitch !
You wait .
You wait till you get to be a man .
( GROWLS )
Baby 's fat .
You fat .
Fat and juicy .
( GROWLS )
( SCREAMS )
( SOBBING )
Oh , that ... that 's not my Bob .
He needs some water .
He needs some water . Would you get it , please ?
MUM : That 's not my Bob !
( SOBBING ) That 's not my Bob !
That 's not my Bob !
Not my Bob !
He wants some water . No , it 's not Bob .
Lynne , Lynne , please , take her to get some water , please .
I 'll take you , Mama .
And some whiskey and blankets too .
- ( SOBS HYSTERICALLY ) That 's not my Bob ! - Whiskey and blankets .
You all right , man ?
What ... what are you doing ? Where are you going ?
You 're not my father .
I 'm going to get those bastards .
- Bobby ? - I will .
( BOB GROANS )
So long , Papa .
Women coming , Mars . Let 's get what we came for and get out .
- Katy ! - What was that ?
Oh , Katy !
Where the hell are you going with my baby ?
Get out of my way , bitch .
( SCREAMS )
Get out of here !
You ...
Take the baby .
You better move your ass .
( SCREAMING )
( GUN CLICKS )
I come back for you later , girlie .
It 's all right ...
It 's all right . It 's all right .
It 's all right , baby . It 's all right .
Don 't go , baby .
Don 't go away .
( SOBS ) Don 't go away .
- ( MOANING ) - OK . OK .
- ( BABY TOY SQUEAKING ) - Oh , Jesus !
Katy ?
Get her inside and see to your mum .
Oh , my God .
( LAUGHS )
Why are you doing this ?
What do you want ?
Damn you !
Give me back my baby .
My Catherine .
( DOG HOWLING )
Please .
( BABY CRYING )
Come on .
Yeah , he 's still got a gun .
Yeah , I got bullets .
( LAUGHING )
Mercury ? You paying attention , Mercury ?
You know how to use that thing ? Huh , Mercury ?
MERCURY : Wait a minute .
I see you ... you got something to eat !
We got the goods , and how , Mercury . ( LAUGHS )
- MERCURY : Is that a baby ? - You be a good , dog , you get some .
Mama Jupi so happy .
Papa Jupi so happy .
Maybe I make a joke like last time and eat the toes .
You think everybody laugh ?
( LAUGHING ) We always laugh at you , Mercury .
Coming through .
OK , Pluto .
( BARKS )
( SCREAMS )
What ?
I thought I heard something , rocks falling .
You got rocks in your head , asshole .
Let 's go .
( WHITE NOISE )
( YELPS )
- I heard you tried to run away . - No , Papa , no .
I heard you messing with Grandpa Fred .
I fixed Grandpa Fred good . ( LAUGHS )
I like fixing people good .
Bobby ?
What you got there ?
Is that what I think it is ?
Oh , yeah .
About time we got some powerful food around here .
- We 're going to eat it , too . - Call in Mercury !
- We don 't need no watch no more . - OK , Papa .
We caught us a young Thanksgiving turkey . ( LAUGHS )
What we going to do ?
They got our food , our ammo ,
they killed Dad and Lynn and they got the baby .
And they 're going to be back .
What are we going to do ?
She hasn 't said a word all night .
Mercury don 't answer , Papa Ju .
Don 't answer ?
Maybe you don 't know how to work it right .
I don 't think that 's it , I told you I heard something .
- You heard what ? - I 'll go find him .
You go do that .
Did you kill them all like I told you to ?
Did you kill them all like I said ?
( SIGHS )
Such a small place , a trailer .
When it 's messy , it 's so messy .
Yeah .
Daddy back yet ?
No , not yet .
Where 's the kids , back yet ?
Yeah , Brenda 's right here and Bobby 's in the kitchen .
Drinking Coke , I bet .
Lynn sleep ?
Yeah .
- ( MUM MOANS ) - Can I get you anything ?
Another blanket , can I have one ?
It 's chilly .
This will keep you warm . This will keep you nice and warm .
( SIGHS ) Thank you .
Thanks .
BRENDA : Oh , no !
- Turn the lights on , please . - Oh Christ , the battery must be dead .
- Bobby , I 'm scared . - I think the bastards took the lantern .
( HYSTERICALLY ) Coming back for me ! Coming to get me , Bobby !
Shut up , will you ?
- I hear them outside . - ( RATTLING )
( SCREAMS )
Shh ! Shh !
- It 's OK . - Maybe I got that son of a bitch .
RADIO : Mercury ? Mercury , you all right ?
Mercury , where are you ?
Cover me .
PLUTO : ( OVER RADIO ) Hello , Papa ? Hello , Papa Jupe ?
MAMA JUPE : ( OVER RADIO ) Hold on Pluto , I 'll get him .
- ( DOG WHINING ) - The beast ?
- That sound like the beast to you ? - I don 't think it was .
Yeah , I think it was .
I 'm telling you , they can do the beast perfect .
BRENDA : Bobby , is it all right ?
- ( DOG BARKS ) - Beast , what are you trying to do ?
Oh , get off of me .
Where have you been ? Huh ? Where have you been ?
You bring this ?
PAPA JUPE : ( OVER RADIO ) This is Jupiter , what you find ?
PLUTO : ( OVER RADIO ) Mercury 's dead , Papa . He 's at the bottom of the cliff .
PAPA JUPE : Mercury 's dead ? He fall ?
PLUTO : He was pushed .
PAPA JUPE : Pushed ? Who the hell pushed my boy ?
PLUTO : Devil dog .
The big bastard 's tracks are right on Mercury 's chest .
Good boy !
PAPA JUPE : Pluto ! You come back here .
We got some things to do . You understand what I 'm saying ?
PLUTO : I 'm coming , Papa .
Uh-oh .
Your dog made sport of my blood , you pig .
I 'm going to kill your kids for that .
You come out here and stick your life in my face .
Stick your fingers in my pie .
That was a bad mistake .
I thought you was smart and tough .
- You 're stupid . - MAMA JUPITER : Yeah , you sure are .
You 're nothing .
I 'm going to watch your goddamn car rust out , yes I will .
Right , Father . Tell him .
I 'll see the wind blow your dried up seeds away .
I 'll eat the heart of your stinking memory .
I 'll eat the brains of your kids ' kids .
I 'm in , you 're out . Mars ?
Yeah , Papa ?
You keep an eye on that young tenderloin baby .
I want nothing happening to her unless I say so .
You get me , Papa . I 'm going with you .
I don 't care .
Well , you got that cut on your legs , a blood pipe as big as your thumb .
Good place to cut somebody , but not so good to get cut there yourself .
Guys !
I got a feeling that tenderloin 's daddy is going to come looking for her .
- You can take care of him then . - I 'll rip his lungs out .
You do that .
- You got bullets for that there cannon ? - All loaded , Papa Jupe .
It 's getting light out .
Let 's get started .
Wait for me .
- ( DOG WHINES ) - Shh !
Bobby ?
Bobby , you read me ?
Shh ! Bobby ?
This is a breaker one-niner for KUY-9532 .
( SOBBING )
BOBBY : Mayday , mayday , mayday . Goddamnit , mayday .
This is a breaker KUY-195 .
Does anybody read this ? This an SOS . Mayday .
This is a breaker one-niner for KUY-9532 .
Does anybody read this ?
- We need police help . - ( BRENDA SOBBING )
Mayday . M ...
Look , Brenda , will you keep it down ?
( SOBBING )
Oh , no .
It 's pretty quiet .
- PLUTO : Think they 're laying for us ? - PAPA JUPE : Wouldn 't be surprised .
BOBBY : Hello , police ? Air Force ?
This is KUY-9532 calling mayday , mayday .
RADIO : Hello KUY , this is Air Force Rescue .
We have you loud and clear . What 's up ?
Thank God . Hello listen , we 're under attack .
I don 't know who . They killed three of us , and they kidnapped a baby .
OK , OK . Now hold on .
What are your defensive capabilities at this time ?
One gun and I only have two bullets left .
We don 't have any hunting rifles or anything .
You 've got to help us . We 're sitting ducks .
Stand by .
You 've got to tell him where we are .
We are recommending that until we can get to you ,
you stand on your heads .
Stand on our heads ? Um , that 's code f ...
Just stand on your heads with your thumbs up your ass .
( LAUGHING )
Oh , Bobby .
( LAUGHING ) " What are your defensive capabilities at this time ? "
Ha ! They 're just sitting ducks .
We 'll go in through that wash . They 'll never see us coming .
PAPA JUPE : ( OVER RADIO ) Mars , we 've seen some signs .
You might have a visitor snooping around .
You keep your eyes open . We 're almost there .
Bobby , do you read me ?
Bobby ?
They 're coming your way .
For Christ 's sake , kid , put your ears on .
Damnit !
Come here , fella . Come here .
Listen , it 's your turn up at the bat , OK ?
So you go and get them , OK ?
Go , go .
Maybe the real Air Force will see this and come .
Forget it .
Nobody 's gonna help us .
We 've got to get out of this ourselves .
Well , if you 've got any bright ideas , girl , just sing right out .
- How strong is this anyway ? - Plenty , why ?
Come on , I got an idea .
( PLUTO SNIFFS )
( BARKING )
Come here !
( SCREAMING ) Papa Jupiter !
Papa Jupiter !
( WHIMPERING )
( BIRD SQUAWKING )
( PLUTO GROANING )
- Mars . - MARS : Did you get them ?
Kill the baby .
- Ruby ? - What do you want ?
- Get it out here . - What ?
- You know what . - What ?
- Just get it out here . - What 's going on ?
Don 't do it until I 'm away . I don 't want to see it .
Ruby !
Where is she ?
Katy !
( BABY CRYING )
Ruby !
( SCREAMING ) Hey , you ! Give me my Katy .
Let 's get out of here !
( SOBBING )
Wait .
What ?
We can 't do this .
We 've got to do it .
It 's the only way to be sure .
( SOBBING )
( GROANING )
( GROWLING )
Fucking devil dog . You son of a bitch !
You piece of shit .
I 'll kill you bitch . I 'll kill you .
I 'll eat your heart , piss licker . Puke eater !
I 'll strangle you with your own guts .
( GRUNTING )
( SCREAMING )
( GASPING )
( SOBS , INDISTINCT )
( BABY CRIES )
- Take the baby , here . - Lift this up .
( PANTING )
( SHOUTING )
( WHEEZING )
You die , boy !
( BABY CRYING )
Jesus , this guy doesn 't quit !
Oh , holy shit !
MARS : Got yourself trapped right where they breed , boy !
Mars ! Take me !
- Get out of here ! - Take me !
You ain 't worth taking , Ruby .
Leave him alone .
Take me .
- Look ! - Ruby !
( BABY CRYING )
Mars !
Katy !
Help !
No !
You ... son of a bitch !
( RATTLING )
You bastard ! You got ten seconds to live .
- Ten seconds ! - ( SHOUTING ) Please !
Get off ! Get off me !
( RATTLING )
Mars !
( BIRD SQUAWKING )
Fire it up .
( ENGINE SPUTTERS )
Come on .
( ENGINE STARTS )
Run !
( SCREAMING )
It 's working .
( ENGINE SPUTTERS )
Shit !
( SCREAMING )
- Come on . - He 's loose !
Hurry !
( SCREAMING )
Hold your nose . Hold your nose .
Through the window , like I told you !
I 'll get you !
Go on . Run !
Come on , open the door .
Come on !
BOTH : Woo-hoo !
- Where are you going ? - We 've got to be sure .
Bobby , don 't !
Bobby , no ! Wait , don 't !
Bobby , don 't leave me ! Don 't leave me !
Bobby , wait !
( SCREAMING ) Bobby !
Bobby , don 't go in there !
Bobby , please don 't go in there !
Bobby ! No ! ( SCREAMING )
Bobby !
( SCREAMING )